In the beginning...
Eternals is a science fiction, action, adventure film directed by Chloé Zhao.
The Eternals are a team of ancient aliens who have been
living on Earth in secret for thousands of years.
When an unexpected tragedy forces them out of the shadows, they are forced to
reunite against mankind’s most ancient enemy, the Deviants.
Sersi, played by Gemma Chan.
Ikaris, played by Richard Madden.
Thena, played by Angelina Jolie.
Ajak, played by Salma Hayek Pinault.
Kingo, played by Kumail Nanjiani.
Sprite, played by Lia McHugh.
Eternals is a 2021 American superhero film based on
the Marvel Comics race the Eternals.
Produced by Marvel Studios and distributed by Walt Disney Studios Motion
Pictures, it is the 26th film in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU).
The film was directed by Chloé Zhao, who wrote the screenplay
with Patrick Burleigh, Ryan Firpo, and Kaz Firpo.
It stars an ensemble cast including Gemma Chan, Richard Madden, Kumail Nanjiani, Lia McHugh, Brian Tyree
Henry, Lauren Ridloff, Barry Keoghan, Don Lee, Kit Harington, Salma Hayek, and Angelina Jolie.
In the film, the Eternals are immortal beings who emerge from hiding after thousands of
years to protect Earth from their ancient counterparts, the Deviants.
In April 2018, Marvel Studios president Kevin Feige announced that a film based on the Eternals was in
development and would explore the group as ancient aliens living throughout human history.
Ryan and Kaz Firpo were hired to write the script, and
Zhao was set to direct in September.
She was given significant creative freedom to rewrite the script, taking particular inspiration from Terrence
Malick's films, and to use more locations and natural lighting than previous MCU films had.
Casting began in early 2019 and Burleigh joined to work on the script ahead of principal photography, which took place
from July 2019 to February 2020 at Pinewood Studios and on location in England and the Canary Islands.
Eternals premiered at the Dolby Theatre in Los Angeles on October 18, 2021, and was
released in the United States on November 5 as part of Phase Four of the MCU.
It grossed $402.1 million worldwide and received several awards and nominations, but it
also became the first MCU film to not receive generally positive reviews.
Particular criticism went to the screenplay and pacing, with commentators feeling it
did not live up to Zhao's previous work or to previous MCU films.
The themes and visuals received some praise.
The film explores themes of superhero, supernatural,
based on comic, alien, super power.
The tone is thought_provoking.